template.net 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy | Template.net

This statement serves as the transparency of Template.net in its commitment to serve the privacy of customers using the website. Please read through the document below to learn more about our privacy policy and how we use information collected from users and visitors.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Template.net does not require visitors to share personal information in the website unless downloading is concerned. When setting up a registered account, you as a member will enter information necessary to support us in contacting you regarding website updates such as  new products and services. By providing Template.net with your personal information, you agree to the use of information in accordance to the privacy policy as outlined in this document.

### NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

Upon receiving and therefore recording non-personal information from users, such as the IP address, cookie information, and requested pages, Template.net reserves the right to make use of such to modify website content. The website shall not connect any of these non-personal data with the personal information collected, as stated in the previous provision.

Upon allowing third-party companies to present advertisements via the Template.net website pages, the third-party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies not covered by Template.net, and we shall not bear any liability for such usage.

### USE OF COOKIES

Visiting Template.net will send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. This helps the website log you in faster, thereby enhancing your navigation experience. Cookies may also help convey information about you and may be used by your browser for subsequent visits to the site. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser, therefore closing once you reset your browser. You may refuse all cookies in your browser, however some features of Template.net may not function properly once this is disabled.

### INFORMATION SHARING DISCLOSURE

Template.net may otherwise disclose personal information upon the following provisions: (1) To respond to any legal proceedings or court orders, (2) to protect the personal safety of website users or to defend the rights of the website as necessary, and (3) upon discovery of visitor actions that violate website guidelines as outlined by official terms and agreements.

To protect the privacy and security of our users, Template.net takes reasonable steps such as requesting email addresses before allowing website downloads. Each user is responsible for maintaining security and account information, and controlling access to email communications with Template.net at all times.

In the event that a user’s personal information is compromised due to breach of security, Template.net will promptly notify the owners of addresses whose personal information has been compromised in accordance with Template.net notification procedures as set forth by this Privacy Policy, or as required by law.

### USER ID TRACKING

Template.net uses Google Analytics to track and analyze website traffic and visitor behavior and usage.

On behalf of the Template.net domain, Google Analytics shall track the flow of users, their locations by country, languages, browsers, operating systems, Internet service providers, and devices used to access the Template.net website.

However, Template.net shall not upload any data that allows Google to identify individuals nor their individually recognized IP addresses.

### CHILD SECURITY

Template.net takes child protection and security seriously. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect personal information of children ages 13 and below. For children under the age of 13, we do not recommend nor encourage sending personal information through Template.net, be it your name, address, telephone number or email address. In the event that Template.net learns we have collected personal information from children below the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, the information will be deleted from our servers as quickly as possible. If you believe that we may have information from children under this age, please send us a message via our [contact page](https://www.template.net/contact-us).

### CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICIES

Template.net reserves the right to alter or modify the current privacy policy at any time, without prior notice to visitors and members, and therefore urges users to review the privacy policy on a regular basis.

### SECURITY

Data is readily available online, however, Template.net assures its visitors and users that the website uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect information transmitted on the website. Along with this, Template.net safeguards personal information from unauthorized access, network firewalls, and other security measures.
